var Questions = { "question" : [
    {
      "question"  : "Which number should come next in the series, 48, 24, 12, ......?",
       "choice1"  : "8",
       "choice2"  : "6",
       "choice3"  : "4",
       "choice4"  : "2",                   
       "correct"  : 2
    },
    
    {
      "question"  : "RQP, ONM, _, IHG, FED, find the missing letters",
       "choice1"  : "CDE",
       "choice2"  : "LKI",
       "choice3"  : "LKJ",
       "choice4"  : "BAC",
       "correct"  : 3
    },
    
    {
      "question"  : " PETAL: FLOWER",
       "choice1"  : "Pen: Paper",
       "choice2"  : "Engine: Car",
       "choice3"  : "Cat: Dog",
       "choice4"  : "Ball: Game",                    
       "correct"  : 2
    },
    
    {
      "question"  : " I. All the colleges in the city had to keep closed for three days a week.II. Many students have left the local colleges.",
       "choice1"  : "Statement II is the cause and statement I is its effect",
       "choice2"  : "Statement I is the cause and statement II is its effect",
       "choice3"  : "Both the statements are effects of independent causes",
       "choice4"  : "Both the statements are independent causes",                   
       "correct"  : 3
    },
    
    {
       "question"  : " Which word does not belong to others?",
       "choice1"  : "Inch",
       "choice2"  : "Kilogram",
       "choice3"  : "Centimeter",
       "choice4"  : "Yard",               
       "correct"  : 2
    },
    {
      "question"  : " Pointing to a photograph, a man said, I have no brother, and that man's father is my father's son.Whose photograph was it?",
       "choice1"  : "His son",
       "choice2"  : "His own",
       "choice3"  : "His father",
       "choice4"  : "His nephew",               
       "correct"  : 1
    },
    {
      "question"  : "Arrange the following words in a meaningful sequence.\n1. Infection\n2. Consultation\n3. Doctor\n4. Treatment\n5. Recovery",
       "choice1"  : "1, 3, 4, 5, 2",
       "choice2"  : "1, 3, 2, 4, 5",
       "choice3"  : "1, 2, 3, 4, 5",
       "choice4"  : "2, 3, 5, 1, 4",               
       "correct"  : 2
    },
    {
      "question"  : "Peter is in the East of Tom and Tom is in the North of John.Mike is in the South of John then in which direction of Peter is Mike?",
       "choice1"  : "South-East",
       "choice2"  : "South-West",
       "choice3"  : "South",
       "choice4"  : "North-East",               
       "correct"  : 2
    },
    {
      "question"  : "Today it is Thursday.After 132 days,it will be",
       "choice1"  : "Monday",
       "choice2"  : "Sunday",
       "choice3"  : "Wednesday",
       "choice4"  : "Thursday",               
       "correct"  : 3
    },
     {
      "question"  : "Complete the series 1,6,13,22,33,...",
       "choice1"  : "46",
       "choice2"  : "48",
       "choice3"  : "49",
       "choice4"  : "51",               
       "correct"  : 1
    },
     {
      "question"  : "At a conference, 12 members shook hands with each other before & after the meeting.How many total number of hand shakes occurred?",
       "choice1"  : "100",
       "choice2"  : "122",
       "choice3"  : "132",
       "choice4"  : "145",               
       "correct"  : 3
    },
     {
      "question"  : "The day after the day after tomorrow is four days before Monday. What day is it today?",
       "choice1"  : "Monday",
       "choice2"  : "Tuesday",
       "choice3"  : "Wednesday",
       "choice4"  : "Thursday",               
       "correct"  : 1
    },
     {
      "question"  : "6, 12, 1, 13, 5 is to flame as 2, 12, 15, 1, 20 is to ?",
       "choice1"  : "voice",
       "choice2"  : "bald",
       "choice3"  : "bloat",
       "choice4"  : "castle",               
       "correct"  : 3
    },
     {
      "question"  : "In alphabet series, some alphabets are missing which are given in that order as one of the alternatives below it.Choose the correct alternative.G4T, J10R, M20P, P43N, S90L",
       "choice1"  : "G4T",
       "choice2"  : "J10R",
       "choice3"  : "M20P",
       "choice4"  : "P43N",               
       "correct"  : 2
    }
<<<<<<< HEAD
]};
=======
    
  ]
  
  };
>>>>>>> 797a37a73102874632f231869e9757d3f0a39aa4
